#### BRANDON ZORNADO

63218 NE Jimbo Ln Bend, OR 97701 Phone: 503-502-7248 Email: bzornado@gmail.com

# PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a professional and highly motivated candidate wanting to apply my educational background and many years of experience by continuing to work in a sales or marketing role. Demonstrated success and knowledge in:

Business Development Team Building
Sales & Marketing Music Licensing
Leadership Customer Service
Sales Force Google Ad Words

Event Planning Promotions/Advertising Google Analytics

Management

#### **EDUCATION**

Western Oregon University March 2008
Major: Bachelor of Science in Business Management GPA 3.5

Minor: Sports Management

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Player's Racquet Shop (Bend, OR)

# Sales & Marketing Operations Director- Oct 2016- October 2017

- Ran all the day-to-day operations of Player's Racquet Shop.
- I was in charge of all product ordering.
- · Handled all marketing aspects to promote and grow the business with a positive image in the community.
- · Organized in store retail displays.
- Set schedules and managed Bend, OR location employees.

#### Sunshine Dairy Foods (Portland, OR)

#### Sales Representative-

#### March 2015- Aug 2015

- Generated and developed new business accounts within a territory to increase revenue.
- Performed maintenance on customer products.
- Effectively planed sales presentations for potential and existing customers.
- Provided product quotes to customers as needed and also delivered product to specific locations.
- Assisted in the forecasting and budget planning with the department sales manager.
- Attended weekly sales meeting with other department managers.
- Performed demo-sampling events of specific product at various retail store locations.
- Attended conferences and trade shows

#### Core Health & Fitness (Star Trac) (Vancouver, WA)

# Inside Sales Representative (East Coast)-

- Handled inbound/ outbound calls using customer service skills.
- Prospected and created new opportunities and passed leads appropriately to nine Territory Managers in the East Coast.

August 2014- March 2015

- Acted as liaison for the Sales Department and between other divisions.
- Followed up on bids, quotations, as well as negotiated and closed sales for commercial fitness equipment.
- Managed on-going relationships with existing customers
- · Monitored performance goals.
- · Traveled to Southern California for team sales meetings.

BusyBee Promotions/ Assist Marketing/ Victory Agency/ ATN Promo/ Event Pro Strategies/ PS-Stearns/ Ascent Talent/ Foley Agency/ EZ Event Promotions/ A + Student Staffing/ PDX Promotions/ CMT Agency (Oregon – Tennessee)

# Brand Ambassador/ Promotional Model/ Event Promotions Manager-

# June 2006- Present

I have been a specialized marketing representative for many major brands. Regular tasks involve working promotional events, providing information about the brand, product or service, generating sales opportunities and working to build customer retention. Some of the bigger name brands that I have worked for and represented our: Nike, ABC TV, Chrysler, Toyota, Hyundai, Ram Trucks, Kellogg's, Post Cereals, Warheads Candy, Bud Light, Budweiser, Stoli Vodka, Starbucks, Cascal Soft Drink, Brew DR Kombucha, Humm Kombucha, Suja Juice, 5-Hour Energy, Naked Juice Vitamin Water, Dads Pet Food, Bunny Bread, Snap- On Tools, Sherwin Williams, T-Mobile, AT&T, All State Insurance, and Geico.

# BMI- Broadcast Music Incorporated (Nashville, TN)

## **Music Licensing Executive-**

## April 2011- Dec 2013

- Sold Music Licenses to commercial business.
- Exceeded sales goals of over \$10,000 monthly
- Collected music licensing fees according to the payment terms in each agreement.
- Made outbound calls and recorded call notes for inbound and outbound calls.
- Responded to customer correspondence.